ChatGPT. A lot of people are saying, "Oh,
you got to use this, you got to..." Keep
it simple. If there are competitors
and outliers,
sometimes you can just copy their
transcript, put it into ChatGPT. What
was in this video? What
are the highlights?
Have a little look through.
This means that when you're doing
competitor homework
and looking at what's doing well for other
people, rather than sitting there
through half-hour videos
and getting bored,
you can nab the transcript from five to
10 different videos, put them all into AI,
and go, "What is the general theme of
all of these?" Then you can go copy all
the comments, put the comments in there,
and go, "What do people like
and dislike about these videos?" Suddenly,
you get
your script to your video
that you've planned and made out.
You put that in there and go,
from all the things you've seen in the
comments and
all the things there,
is there anything missing from my video?
What would you put in? Then
if you wanted to go a step further,
you could say, "In
my writing style,
could you expand into those points
that you thought I should have
in my video?" That's why I think it's
pretty good.